export default class Question2 {
  public static question: Question2[] = [
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to use different passwords for various online accounts?',
      answers: [
        'A It is not necessary; the same password can be used for convenience',
        'B To avoid the hassle of remembering multiple passwords',
        'C To minimize the risk of multiple accounts being compromised if one password is leaked',
        'D To make it easier for password recovery',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C To minimize the risk of multiple accounts being compromised if one password is leaked',
      explanation: 'To minimize the risk of multiple accounts being compromised if one password is leaked',
    },
    {
      question: ' Which of the following is an example of a strong password policy?',
      answers: [
        'A Allowing users to use the same password for multiple accounts',
        'B Requiring passwords to be at least 8 characters long',
        'C Discouraging the use of special characters in passwords',
        'D Implementing no restrictions on password complexity'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Requiring passwords to be at least 8 characters long',
      explanation: 'Requiring passwords to be at least 8 characters long',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can a passphrase be more secure than a single-word password?',
      answers: [
        'A Passphrases are always less secure',
        'B Passphrases are easier to crack',
        'C Passphrases are longer and include spaces between words',
        'D Passphrases are less memorable'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Passphrases are longer and include spaces between words',
      explanation: 'Passphrases are longer and include spaces between words',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the recommended frequency for changing passwords to enhance security?',
      answers: [
        'A Every month',
        'B Only when a security breach occurs',
        'C Every few years',
        'D Never, if the password is strong and unique'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'D Never, if the password is strong and unique',
      explanation: 'Never, if the password is strong and unique',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following password management practices is insecure',
      answers: [
        'A Using a password manager to generate and store complex passwords',
        'B Writing down passwords on a sticky note and keeping it on the monitor',
        'C Changing passwords every few years',
        'D Sharing passwords with close family members'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Writing down passwords on a sticky note and keeping it on the monitor',
      explanation: 'Writing down passwords on a sticky note and keeping it on the monitor',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following passwords is the most secure?',
      answers: [
        'A password123',
        'B P@ssw0rd',
        'C qwerty',
        'D 123456'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B P@ssw0rd',
      explanation: 'P@ssw0rd',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a recommended practice for creating strong passwords?',
      answers: [
        'A Using easily memorable phrases',
        'B Incorporating personal information like birthdates',
        'C Using a mix of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols',
        'D Keeping the same password across multiple accounts'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Using a mix of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols',
      explanation: 'Using a mix of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to avoid using easily guessable passwords?',
      answers: [
        'A Because they are easier to remember',
        'B To make it more challenging for unauthorized access',
        'C They are less likely to be accepted by websites',
        'D To confuse the user'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B To make it more challenging for unauthorized access',
      explanation: 'To make it more challenging for unauthorized access',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of Two-Factor Authentication (2FA)?',
      answers: [
        'A Enhancing password security by requiring two different passwords',
        'B Providing a second layer of verification in addition to a password',
        'C Encrypting all data on a device',
        'D Allowing access without any authentication'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Providing a second layer of verification in addition to a password',
      explanation: 'Providing a second layer of verification in addition to a password',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is considered a strong password practice?',
      answers: [
        'A Using easily guessable words like "password123"',
        'B Using a combination of uppercase and lowercase letters',
        'C Sharing passwords with trusted friends',
        'D Keeping the same password for all accounts'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Using a combination of uppercase and lowercase letters',
      explanation: 'Using a combination of uppercase and lowercase letters',
    },
  ];

  public static dumpQuestions: Question2[] = [];
}
